{
	"questionList": {
		"2018-12-04": {
			"question": "When was wells fargo founded?",
			"answer": "March 18,1852",
			"option1": "March 18,1852",
			"option1": "March 18,1862",
			"option1": "June 18,1852"
		},
		"2018-12-05": {
			"question": "How many Wells Fargo ATM's?",
			"answer": "13000",
			"option1": "13000",
			"option1": "16000",
			"option1": "14000"
		},
		"2018-12-06": {
			"question": "Where do they take the team members who won WAC?",
			"answer": "Dubai",
			"option1": "Dubai",
			"option1": "Europe tour",
			"option1": "Singapore"
		},
		"2018-12-07": {
			"question": "Where was wells fargo founded?",
			"answer": "New York,NY",
			"option1": "New York,NY",
			"option1": "Phoenix",
			"option1": "California"
		},
		"2018-12-08": {
			"question": "What's not wells fargo's vision?",
			"answer": "Shareholder value",
			"option1": "Shareholder value",
			"option1": "What's right for customers",
			"option1": "Diversity and inclusion"
		},
		"2018-12-09": {
			"question": "When was wells fargo founded?",
			"answer": "March 18,1852",
			"option1": "March 18,1852",
			"option1": "March 18,1862",
			"option1": "June 18,1852"
		},
		"2018-12-10": {
			"question": "How many Wells Fargo ATM's?",
			"answer": "13000",
			"option1": "13000",
			"option1": "16000",
			"option1": "14000"
		},
		"2018-12-11": {
			"question": "Where do they take the team members who won WAC?",
			"answer": "Dubai",
			"option1": "Dubai",
			"option1": "Europe tour",
			"option1": "Singapore"
		},
		"2018-12-12": {
			"question": "Where was wells fargo founded?",
			"answer": "New York,NY",
			"option1": "New York,NY",
			"option1": "Phoenix",
			"option1": "California"
		},
		"2018-12-13": {
			"question": "What's not wells fargo's vision?",
			"answer": "Shareholder value",
			"option1": "Shareholder value",
			"option1": "What's right for customers",
			"option1": "Diversity and inclusion"
		},
		"2018-12-14": {
			"question": "When was wells fargo founded?",
			"answer": "March 18,1852",
			"option1": "March 18,1852",
			"option1": "March 18,1862",
			"option1": "June 18,1852"
		},
		"2018-12-15": {
			"question": "How many Wells Fargo ATM's?",
			"answer": "13000",
			"option1": "13000",
			"option1": "16000",
			"option1": "14000"
		},
		"2018-12-16": {
			"question": "Where do they take the team members who won WAC?",
			"answer": "Dubai",
			"option1": "Dubai",
			"option1": "Europe tour",
			"option1": "Singapore"
		},
		"2018-12-17": {
			"question": "Where was wells fargo founded?",
			"answer": "New York,NY",
			"option1": "New York,NY",
			"option1": "Phoenix",
			"option1": "California"
		},
		"2018-12-18": {
			"question": "What's not wells fargo's vision?",
			"answer": "Shareholder value",
			"option1": "Shareholder value",
			"option1": "What's right for customers",
			"option1": "Diversity and inclusion"
		}
	}
}